<customerDialogue>
    <opening mood="high">
        <line>Finally! I've been searching every stall in the city for this.</line>
        <line>By the gods, it's beautiful. What's the damage, shopkeep?</line>
        <line>You have a keen eye for stock. How much for this piece?</line>
        <line>This is just the thing I've been looking for. What do you want for it?</line>
        <line>I must have this. Tell me your price!</line>
    </opening>

    <opening mood="medium">
        <line>This caught my eye. What's your asking price?</line>
        <line>I could use another one of these. What are you charging?</line>
        <line>Let's talk business. What's the sticker price on this?</line>
        <line>Not bad at all. How much are you looking to get?</line>
        <line>I've seen worse quality. What's your best offer?</line>
    </opening>

    <opening mood="low">
        <line>I'm in a hurry, so let's keep this quick. Price?</line>
        <line>I'm not here for small talk. What do you want for this?</line>
        <line>I hope you aren't planning on overcharging me. How much?</line>
        <line>My purse is light today, so be gentle. What's the cost?</line>
        <line>It's a bit dusty, isn't it? What's your price?</line>
    </opening>

    <rejection patience="high">
        <line>You've got a sense of humor, I'll give you that. Try again.</line>
        <line>A bit rich for my blood. Can we find a middle ground?</line>
        <line>I like you, but I don't like that price. Lower it.</line>
        <line>Let's be realistic here. That's a bit high, isn't it?</line>
        <line>I'm interested, but not at that price. Come down a bit.</line>
    </rejection>

    <rejection patience="medium">
        <line>We're drifting apart here. Give me a real number.</line>
        <line>That's more than I'm willing to part with. Do better.</line>
        <line>You're trying to retire on one sale! Lower it.</line>
        <line>My interest is fading as fast as my patience. Better price?</line>
        <line>I can get this for half that in the next town over.</line>
    </rejection>

    <rejection patience="low">
        <line>One more price like that, and I'm out the door.</line>
        <line>Don't take me for a fool. Give me your absolute best price now.</line>
        <line>My boots are already pointed toward the exit. Last chance.</line>
        <line>I've got better things to do than listen to these prices. Final offer?</line>
        <line>You're wasting my time. Give me a reason to stay.</line>
    </rejection>

    <walkaway>
        <line>Keep it then. I hope it rots on your shelf.</line>
        <line>I'm not paying those prices. I'm going elsewhere.</line>
        <line>What a joke. Try being a merchant instead of a thief.</line>
        <line>I'm done here. You've lost a customer today.</line>
        <line>I'll find it cheaper at the market. Goodbye.</line>
        <line>Life's too short for this. I'm leaving.</line>
        <line>You'll never sell anything at those rates. Good luck.</line>
    </walkaway>

    <success value="great">
        <line>A steal! I'll be telling everyone about your shop.</line>
        <line>Now that's what I call a bargain! Much appreciated.</line>
        <line>I feel like I'm the one robbing you! Deal!</line>
        <line>Incredible. You've got yourself a regular customer now.</line>
        <line>Splendid! This is why I love shopping here.</line>
    </success>

    <success value="fair">
        <line>Seems right to me. You've got a deal.</line>
        <line>I can live with that. Here is your gold.</line>
        <line>Reasonable enough. Let's shake on it.</line>
        <line>A fair trade for a fair item. Thank you.</line>
        <line>Agreed. It's a deal.</line>
    </success>

    <success value="steep">
        <line>You're a shark, you know that? Fine, I'll take it.</line>
        <line>My wallet is crying, but I need the item. Here.</line>
        <line>I'm paying for the convenience, clearly. Take your coin.</line>
        <line>You won this round, merchant. Don't expect me back soon.</line>
        <line>It’s overpriced, but I'm desperate. Fine.</line>
    </success>
</customerDialogue>